{
    "id": "240476d15bd64c4b845ffe4055a07554",
    "title": "Change Into Passive Voice",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I write short stories. / Short stories ............................ by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are writing",
                "are written",
                "have written"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e715ed0a457c4cf8a5b3b0e3ebbf7e7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "All children watch cartoon programs. / Cartoon programs ...................... by all children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have watched",
                "are watched",
                "were watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "274427bbfaeb4bbf83db0d83b14462ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "He helps his wife. / His wife ....................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "helped",
                "is helped",
                "has helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35e255213e9447a1a86364d6f307d074"
        },
        {
            "question": "Masons build houses. / Houses ...................... by masons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "built",
                "are building",
                "are built"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f2ced8e2ad844fbbfba9fa9b449cd6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am writing a story. / A story ........................ by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is written",
                "is being written",
                "been written",
                "has been written"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9b3a0e0c708404e815b0b7fdab8815f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are planting flowers in the garden. / Flowers ..................... in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are planting",
                "are being planted",
                "are planted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "782706dfc7a14339bc9995617c35d2bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys are making a toy car. / A toy car ................... by the boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is made",
                "is being made",
                "is making"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5203cb07791943d7a143fd0b22fa3935"
        },
        {
            "question": "The washer man is washing the clothes. / The clothes ............................. by the washer man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are being washed",
                "are washing",
                "are washed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "081287f63d4e4136bfbdd9fd571746d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The goat is eating the leaves. / The leaves ............................ by the goat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are being eaten",
                "are eating",
                "have been eating"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f49737f1dd347acb99d4621cd6b21b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is singing a song. / A song .............................. by her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been sung",
                "is sung",
                "is being sung"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2a51b7542086427bb507dc584d1ead8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have finished the job. / The job .............................. by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has finished",
                "has been finishing",
                "has been finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e8806282ec0b4e03930ef7c3f3eac12b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju has broken another window. / Another window ............................ by Raju.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is broken",
                "had broken",
                "has been broken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "88540413ce094b73a7047e75ac4bd359"
        }
    ]
}